<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Aron</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Aron</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Accomplishments</title><link>/accomplishments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/accomplishments/</guid><description>There aren&amp;rsquo;t many. I&amp;rsquo;m an risk-averse underachiever and having a legacy isn&amp;rsquo;t important to me. However, I&amp;rsquo;m not above bragging a bit about what little I&amp;rsquo;ve managed to do with my life.
I once biked about 400 miles from Dobbs Ferry, New York to Montreal, Canada. It took a few weeks, and involved camping and carrying associated paraphernelia on my bike.
It would&amp;rsquo;ve been cooler if I did it alone, but it was part of a summer program with a group.</description></item><item><title>Bicycling</title><link>/bicycling/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/bicycling/</guid><description>My parents were divorced and lived about 90 minutes apart, so I spent a good deal of time in the car growing up.
I was, and still am, very susceptible to motion sickness, and even the smell of cars induces nausea for me. I was involved in a couple of car accidents growing up, from which I developed anxiety about being in a car, constantly on edge and unable to relax.</description></item><item><title>Identity</title><link>/identity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/identity/</guid><description>Generally I place more weight in personal choices and self-expression than the immutable characteristics people are assigned at birth.
The things I identify with the most are my hobbies, interests, and personal views, many of which are detailed on this website. All of the below is just stuff I&amp;rsquo;m gonna go into because it&amp;rsquo;s a personal website and doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter too much to me.
So yeah, in case you are actually curious about my identity in the traditional sense, I&amp;rsquo;m 21 years old and a he/him identifier.</description></item><item><title>Music</title><link>/music/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/music/</guid><description>I listen to electronic music pretty much exclusively. None of it is the type of electronic music that&amp;rsquo;s socially acceptable to listen to.
Here are five songs that encapsulate my taste well.
Candid Oak - Grasp Culprate &amp;amp; Dexcell - Poison Distayne - Far Away emelka &amp;amp; Nyah - Land of Lanterns KERO - Rainforest Potentially you&amp;rsquo;ll like one of these.</description></item><item><title>Name</title><link>/name/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/name/</guid><description>The name Aron doesn&amp;rsquo;t really mean anything. It&amp;rsquo;s an unusual spelling of Aaron that my parents gave me because they felt like it.
It&amp;rsquo;s supposed to be pronounced /ærɪn/ (like the a in &amp;ldquo;ash&amp;rdquo;) but I guess Aaron is pronounced like /ɛrɪn/ (like &amp;ldquo;air-in&amp;rdquo;) so I&amp;rsquo;m mostly called that. Language is fluid so whatever. Whenever people ask I tell them to pronounce it the way they normally would.</description></item><item><title>NYC</title><link>/nyc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/nyc/</guid><description>I grew up here and consider it my home. If all goes well I&amp;rsquo;ll be living here for the rest of my days.
My great-great-grandparents emigrated here from the Soviet Union in the 1920s when anti-semitism was ramping up throughout Europe.
That story doesn&amp;rsquo;t really matter besides the fact that I have an established familial presence in the city and I have the uncommon opportunity to live here into adulthood without paying exorbitant rent.</description></item><item><title>privacy</title><link>/privacy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/privacy/</guid><description>privacy is a human right, whether it be in real life or on the internet. to reflect that, this website does not track, gather information about, or profile its users in any way. feel free to browse this website without limits; your activity will be completely unmonitored.
below is a list of invasive technologies you will not find on this website.
tracking cookies ip logging analytics advertising however, this website does contain links to other websites and with their own privacy policies.</description></item><item><title>Website</title><link>/website/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/website/</guid><description>I have no need for a public website, I just think they&amp;rsquo;re cool. I don&amp;rsquo;t have a company, brand, or social media presence to promote. I&amp;rsquo;m just a guy.
However I do like doing this &amp;ldquo;kind of thing&amp;rdquo; in my spare time. I don&amp;rsquo;t work in tech or develop websites for my job or anything like that. Just a random pursuit I did online because I wanted to. This webpage is kind of pointless but I hope that tells you something about me.</description></item></channel></rss>