<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>home on aron online!</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content in home on aron online!</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Candid Keyboard</title><link>/projects/a-candid-keyboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/projects/a-candid-keyboard/</guid><description>Our world demands that a significant portion of human uptime be spent on a screen, whether it be for work, academia, or even leisure. Over the past year I&amp;rsquo;ve taken an interest in optimizing my online efficiency to reduce the time I need to spend online. I reckoned with this by attempting to master the devices that are responsible for bridging the interactional gap between us and our computers: keyboards. Improving my typing speed seemed like an obvious first step.</description></item><item><title>Cars vs. People</title><link>/writing/cars-vs.-people/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/writing/cars-vs.-people/</guid><description>Rugged individualism is the frequently touted idea that in the United States, you succeed solely on your own merits, accepting no handouts. The philosophy has been steadily ingrained in the American psyche since the conception of the country, which was sold to immigrants as a place where social and economic mobility exists through hard work alone. Most will be familiar with the concept by another glamorized term: the &amp;ldquo;American Dream&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Materials Project</title><link>/projects/materials-project/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/projects/materials-project/</guid><description>For my materials class, students were assigned the task of designing and conducting a semester-long lab experiment to test the mechanical properties of a material of our choosing. Due to my newfound obsession with keyboards, I decided to test thermoplastics, as they are commonly used in keyboard switches. Ultimately, it was a valuable first foray into engineering lab work. Being able to interface with genuine lab equipment and use real data to write a scientific paper was a fulfilling experience.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>/privacy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/privacy/</guid><description>Privacy Policy In my opinion, everyone deserves the right to privacy in all facets of life. To reflect that, this website does not track, gather information about, or profile its users in any way. Feel free to browse this website without limits; your activity will be completely unmonitored.
Below is a list of invasive technologies you will not find on this website.
Tracking cookies IP logging Analytics Third-party advertising However, this website does contain links to other websites and with their own privacy policies.</description></item></channel></rss>