<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Personal on Aron</title><link>/personal/</link><description>Recent content in Personal on Aron</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bicycling</title><link>/personal/bicycling/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/personal/bicycling/</guid><description>This is a chronological account of my experiences with cycling, with a distribution of about 50% memoir and 50% op-ed.
During middle school I got my first bike, a &amp;ldquo;hybrid&amp;rdquo; Trek FX 2. My dad and I spent a couple of summers riding a section of the Heritage Trail, a rail-trail in Orange County, semi-regularly. I have very fond memories of those rides and they kickstarted what will presumably be a lifelong love of cycling.</description></item><item><title>Concerts</title><link>/personal/concerts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/personal/concerts/</guid><description>The following is an archive and retrospective of my concertgoing experiences, in reverse chronological order.
Chime - Aetherborne Tour May 6th, 2023 Brooklyn Meadows, NYC Openers: Skybreak, D3vinity, She, Swole Sauce, ILL EYEZ
Crankdat - Return of the Crank Tour February 24, 2023 Royale, Boston Openers: Ace Aura, some local DJs
Ace Aura&amp;rsquo;s set was fucking awesome. Before the
acloudyskye, Dobi, eliderp, luminism, Skybreak, &amp;amp; torr - FORMFEST June 25, 2022 Mercury Lounge, NYC</description></item><item><title>Keyboards</title><link>/personal/keyboards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/personal/keyboards/</guid><description>I type on a split, ergonomic, 34-key keyboard.
This is the result of a rabbit hole I went down in 2021 or so. In retrospect it was quite a valuable hobby to pick up; I learned how to solder microelectronics, the basics of PCB design, and to this day I type faster and more efficiently than I ever did before.
Sweep The first keyboard I built, without any experience soldering or working with a bill of materials, was the Sweep, a popular open-source keyboard design.</description></item><item><title>Music Taste</title><link>/personal/music-taste/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/personal/music-taste/</guid><description>Here are five songs that encapsulate my taste well. All links are to Bandcamp.
Candid Oak - Grasp Culprate &amp;amp; Bloom - Aurora emelka &amp;amp; Nyah - Land of Lanterns Former Hero - redwood RefraQ &amp;amp; Chalky - Fold Hopefully you enjoy one of them. This is a very limited selection of my favorite music, so if you want to know more, talk to me! Music is my favorite artform and I enjoy getting into the weeds about it.</description></item><item><title>Name</title><link>/personal/name/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/personal/name/</guid><description>The name Aron doesn&amp;rsquo;t really mean anything. It&amp;rsquo;s little more than an unusual spelling of Aaron.
According to my parents it&amp;rsquo;s supposed to be pronounced /ærɪn/ (like the a in &amp;ldquo;ash&amp;rdquo;) but I guess Aaron is pronounced like /ɛrɪn/ (like &amp;ldquo;air-in&amp;rdquo;) so I&amp;rsquo;m mostly called that. Language is fluid so I let it slide. Whenever people ask I tell them to pronounce it the way they normally would.</description></item></channel></rss>